[{"answer": "It was bad.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "How bad was the damage there?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "You know, government officials there have told us they believe it's intimidation of him.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Do you believe that the intended target was Colonel Gadhafi himself?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "I found this unimaginable, hypocritical, irresponsible, and outrageous.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "It was called off at the last moment today because of journalists including yourself being taken to the compound and being used perhaps as some form of human shield, what was your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "It was expected that they would be released sooner than they were.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Late breaking tonight in the papers, very harrowing details of the ordeal that they went through, but what have you picked up so far?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Well, here's the capital - the city of Benghazi rather is fairly quiet - the de facto capital of the opposition-controlled eastern part of the country.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Arwa, what's going on in Benghazi tonight?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, to put it in the simplest of terms.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "There seems to be lots of conjecture about exactly who they are and whether we should be supporting them?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "A bit, Piers.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Are you confused?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "From a military perspective, clearly already it seems to be at least a messy operation because the message is not being communicated about what we are doing.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "What kind of Libya would they choose to construct?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "It's a great question.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "How does America and the allied forces with America it shall how do they declare victory?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "That brings up a great question, Piers.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Where does it stop?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "General, thank you very much indeed for your time.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "How long are we willing to sustain this at the level of resources and policy?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Politically the president is getting criticism from the right and from his own Democratic left.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Wolf, from what the general was just telling me this is already a mess, isn't it, politically?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "He probably should have delivered an oval office address to the nation just before the U.S. Tomahawk cruise missiles were launched.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Wolf, finally, quickly, do you think President Obama now needs to re-clarify the mission here so that everyone's under no misunderstanding about exactly what is going on?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Well, I think the people that know Gadhafi close, they are sure that Gadhafi will not give up.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "What do you think the Gadhafi regime will do now as the coalition begins to turn on him and perhaps circle him?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I think the Arab League for the first time, they stand by the people, and I believe the Arab nations, they are supporting us, and some of them are very involved with supporting the Libyan people.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Ambassador, will the Arab league's endorsement for this action endure, or do you sense there is growing disquiet amongst some of the Arab League leaders that the actions going on now go much further than simply enforcing a no-fly zone?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Well, the opposition is the whole Libyan people.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "How do you see the future with the protesters?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Is there an Islamist element to the opposition?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "I think it will not last much if the attacks on his forces continue.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Finally, Ambassador, and quickly, please, how long do you think this will take for Gadhafi to be defeated?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "I think the ambassador just told you what would have happened if we hadn't done this, which would have been a bloodbath in Benghazi that make what's happened already seem like child's play.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Why do you think this is such a good idea?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "We need a policy in every one of these cases.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "How far do you take this?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I do think it will be enough.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "You believe that this is too late in the day, but will it be enough now that we have finally taken action?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "I think there is a lack of clarity.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Are you clear what it is?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "OLFOWITZ: That's unacceptable.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "What if, as with Saddam Hussein, the no-fly zone continues for 12 years?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "Should we go in there as well, in your opinion?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "It's going to be difficult because the mission, in my judgment, is not yet clear.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "How do you think President Obama has been handling this crisis?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Regarding what's going on here, you can see this picture behind me, Piers.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "What is the current situation in Japan, in particular in relation to the ongoing nuclear crisis?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "I mean, you know, the word trust and the word government is not necessarily synonymous, no matter where you go in the world.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "What do you hear about that?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I think we're going to see more bombing of more targets, maybe some here in Tripoli, certainly taking out the remaining air defense and radar installations along the coasts of that no-fly zone, gets extended all the way past Tripoli here.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "What do you anticipate will happen in the next 24 hours?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "You know, really there isn't.", "docId": "110321pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Is there any sign that the Gadhafi regime is cracking under the initial pressure of coalition air strikes?", "qSentId": 489}]